[{
    "question": "What is Mardi Gras New Orleans?",
    "choice1": "festival",
    "choice2": "legend",
    "choice3": "summer camp",
    "choice4": "human",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not one of New Orleans' Mardi Gras colors?",
    "choice1": "green",
    "choice2": "yellow",
    "choice3": "blue",
    "choice4": "purple",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the New Orleans Mardi Gras colors is not a Mobilian Mardi Gras color?",
    "choice1": "yellow",
    "choice2": "purple",
    "choice3": "blue",
    "choice4": "green",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What medieval tradition can Mardi Gras be traced back to?",
    "choice1": "parading held in celebration of Lent",
    "choice2": "feasting before the arrival of Lent",
    "choice3": "the throwing of trinkets by children to celebrate Lent",
    "choice4": "ordinary citizens dressing in costume to celebrate Lent",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the first mystic society, created in 1830?",
    "choice1": "cowbellion de Rakin Society",
    "choice2": "the Lost Cause Minstrels",
    "choice3": "crewe of Comos",
    "choice4": "order of Myths",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "WWhen did this original mystic society hold its parade?",
    "choice1": "Easter Sunday",
    "choice2": "Mardi Gras Day",
    "choice3": "New Year's Eve",
    "choice4": "Christmas Eve",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "How did the Spanish add their touch to the French Mardi Gras?",
    "choice1": "by changing the name to 'Martes Gordo'",
    "choice2": "by holding lighted torch parades",
    "choice3": "by throwing woven Spanish dolls off of the floats",
    "choice4": "by marching on a different day",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following was New Orleans' first mystic society?",
    "choice1": "crewe of Columbus",
    "choice2": "order of Inca",
    "choice3": "crewe of Comos",
    "choice4": "comic Cowboys",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following individuals gained fame for reviving Mardi Gras after the Civil War?",
    "choice1": "Ethel Hodgson",
    "choice2": "Michael Kraft",
    "choice3": "Joseph Cain",
    "choice4": "Daniel E. Huger",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following societies did Joseph Cain found?",
    "choice1": "Crewe of Comos",
    "choice2": "Order of Myths",
    "choice3": "Strikers Independent Society",
    "choice4": "Mystics of Time",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the first black mystic society in Mobile?",
    "choice1": "Knights of May Zulu Club",
    "choice2": "Colored Carnival Association",
    "choice3": "Order of Mammoths",
    "choice4": "Order of Doves",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following was Mobile's first women's society?",
    "choice1": "Polka Dots",
    "choice2": "Le Krewe de Bienville",
    "choice3": "Order of Athena",
    "choice4": "Mystical Ladies",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Mardi Gras known as in the Christian calendar?",
    "choice1": "Shrove Tuesday",
    "choice2": "Lent",
    "choice3": "Ash Tuesday",
    "choice4": "Happy Tuesday",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What Mobilian mystic society rides aboard floats that are decorated with sarcastic remarks and drawings and rarely throws candy and trinkets?",
    "choice1": "Comic Cowboys",
    "choice2": "Krewe of Goats",
    "choice3": "Knights of Revelry",
    "choice4": "Order of Athena",
    "answer": 1
  }
]